wpr.org 2014-11-11

# Privacy Policy | Wisconsin Public Radio

Protecting the privacy of our Web site visitors is very important us. Because we gather certain types of information about our visitors, we want to make sure you are informed of the ways in which we may and may not use the information you transmit to us when you visit us. This statement discloses the privacy practices for all WPR Web sites including the [Wisconsin Public Radio Association](http://wpra.org/) member support site.

### Voluntarily-Supplied Information

We will not collect personally identifiable information from you, other than what you supply to us on a voluntary basis. To make use of certain features on our web sites, you may need to register and provide some information as part of the registration process. The information you supply helps us offer you more personalized features, tailoring our site to your interests and making it more useful to you.

In order to participate in some activities, you may be asked to provide some personally identifiable information so we can continually improve the services we offer. For example, we need to know your e-mail address to send you electronic newsletters and for you to participate online in various activities. Knowing some of your program preferences can help us send information tailored to your interests. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary.

The areas of the site in which we collect such information, the information collected and the purpose for collecting that information are described below:

### Online Pledges and Purchases

WPR's Web site offers you the convenience of making membership contributions and other purchases via credit card. We take seriously the security of your account information. As with credit card transactions made over the phone or in person, your credit card information is used only for the purchase or contribution you wish to make.

When making an online pledge, you must provide your name, mailing address, home telephone number, contribution level and credit card or other payment information. This is the same information we ask of all contributors in order to process pledges. In addition, Online contributors must also supply their e-mail addresses. You also have the option of supplying a telephone number.

You can purchase various items through our Web sites. When making an online purchase, you must provide your name, mailing address, home telephone number, e-mail address and credit card payment information. This information is also handled through our secure server and is required to process and ship orders. This information will not be disclosed to any third party.

Our Web transaction forms are stored and served from a secure server. This means that all information flowing between your computer and our server is encrypted, so in the highly unlikely event that your transmission is intercepted, it will not be usable. The web address of these forms will start with "https" and most browsers will show that the session is encrypted with an icon next to the address or elsewhere on the screen.

### Volunteer opportunities

If you would like to volunteer your time to support WPR, you can do so through an online form on our Web site. In order to register as a volunteer, you must provide your name, mailing address, daytime and evening telephone numbers and your e-mail address. This information makes it possible for us to notify you of volunteer opportunities. Other details you provide in the online form help us match your interests with our needs.

### Subscription to Electronic Newsletters

WPR offers free electronic newsletters to users. These newsletters include highlights of WPR programming, daily program schedules and other information of interest to our listeners and supporters. To subscribe, you must provide your e-mail address. To remove yourself from the mailing list, follow the instructions at the bottom of any newsletter.

### Feedback, Requests and Suggestions

WPR uses several e-mail forms throughout its Web sites such as on our "Listener Feedback" page, our "Comments & Suggestions" page, and on our "Classics by Request" page. In most cases, we request your name, e-mail address and other information such as your comments, suggestions or musical requests. In addition, some forms give you the option of entering a city and state. This information is used to respond to your comments and it may be used in aggregate form for statistical purposes.

### Surveys

WPR may occasionally conduct a survey with the option of participating through wpr.org. Apart from program preference information you provide, survey responses are not correlated to any personally identifying information and are used in aggregate form to help us tailor WPR's broadcast and online services to your needs.

### Anonymous statistics

All Web servers automatically collect and log limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet when you visit our sites. The information allows us to make our web site more useful to our visitors. We do NOT record your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, or any other personally-identifying information. Rather, we log some or all of the following information:

  * The IP or Internet Protocol Address of the machine you used to access our web site.
  * The date and time you visited.
  * The pages or files you viewed or downloaded from our site.
  * The browser used.
  * The operating system used by your computer.
  * The screen resolution you used to view our pages.
  * The amount of time you spent viewing or listening to our streaming media files.

This data DOES NOT contain any personally identifiable information. We use the data for analyzing Web site traffic and making improvements for visitors to our Web sites.

### Tracking and Use of Cookies

To help make our sites more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature found in browser software, called a "cookie" to assign each visitor a unique, anonymous user ID that resides only on your computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won't know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. A cookie can not read data stored on your computer.

We use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs and to deliver a better, more personalized service. We may also use cookies to track the pages on our site visited by our users. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often.

### Policies for Children

WPR will not knowingly accept personally identifiable information from visitors under the age of 18 who have not obtained permission from their parents or guardians. If your child sends us an e-mail with a request, question or comment, or enters a contest, we will respond using his or her e-mail and will not store it for future communications.

### External Links

Our Web pages may contain links to other commercial, non-commercial and educational sites related to our programming, projects and underwriting. Policies on these sites may vary from those of wpr.org.

We assume responsibility only for the information provided by Wisconsin Public Radio on this site. As a convenience, there are links throughout our Web sites that allow you to leave WPR's sites. You should be aware that these linked sites are not under WPR control. We can make no representations to you concerning the content of these sites, nor does the fact that WPR provides a link serve as an endorsement by WPR of any of these sites. You should also be aware that the privacy protections afforded by the WPR Web site may not be afforded by sites linked to and from the WPR sites.

### Acceptance of the wpr.org Privacy Policy

By using this Web site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this WPR Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of WPR's web sites following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.

Note that we may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the WPR web site; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).
